A Guide to the JDR 3rd Fund records FA081
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Arts in Education Program - Jane Remer Files, 1972-1979; 10; 15.5 Cubic Feet 31 document cases
  - Arts in Education Program - Jane Remer Files - Contact File, 10.C
    - Educational Organizations - Public Education Association, 1975 (Box 91, Folder 765)
    - Educational Organizations - Southern Columbia University Project, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 766)
    - Educational Organizations - Teacher's College (Columbia University), 1973-1978 (Box 91, Folder 767)
    - Educational Organizations - Teacher's and Writers Collaborative, 1974-1975 (Box 91, Folder 768)
    - Educational Organizations - Technical Education Research Center, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 769)
    - Foundations - General Material, 1975-1978 (Box 92, Folder 770)
    - Foundations (A-F) (Box 92, Folder 771)
    - Foundations - New York City Cultural Council, 1973-1978 (Box 92, Folder 772)
    - Foundations - New York Community Trust Foundation, 1974-1978 (Box 92, Folder 773)
    - Foundations - New York Community Trust Foundation, 1974-1978 (Box 92, Folder 774)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 92, Folder 775)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Miscellany, 1974-1978 (Box 92, Folder 776)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Artist in Schools Program, 1974-1978 (Box 92, Folder 777)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Dance Program Meeting, June 3, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 778)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Emergency School Aid Act (ESAA) Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 93, Folder 779)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Proposals, 1975-1979 (Box 93, Folder 780)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Proposals, 1975-1979 (Box 93, Folder 781)
    - Foundations - New York Foundation for the Arts - Proposals, 1975-1979 (Box 93, Folder 782)
    - Foundations (No-Z) (Box 93, Folder 783)
    - Museums - General Material, 1973-1976 (Box 93, Folder 784)
    - Museums Collaborative, 1972-1978 (Box 93, Folder 785)
      Funded by a grant from the New York State Council on the Arts to meet the needs of major New York City cultural institutions.
    - Museums - Museum of Modern Art - Children's Art Carnival, 1972-1978 (Box 94, Folder 786)
    - Museums - Whitney Museum of Art, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 787)
    - Music Organizations - General Material, 1973-1976 (Box 94, Folder 788)
    - Music Organizations - American Symphony Orchestra, 1974-1976 (Box 94, Folder 789)
    - Music Organizations - Kodaly Institute - Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 94, Folder 790)
    - Music Organizations - Kodaly Institute - Proposal to Exxon, 1975-1976 (Box 94, Folder 791)
    - Music Organizations - Kodaly Institute - Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 94, Folder 792)
    - Music Organizations - Metropolitan Opera Association, 1976-1978 (Box 94, Folder 793)
    - Music Organizations - Music America, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 794)
    - Music Organizations - New York Jazz Museum, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 795)
    - Music Organizations - New York Philharmonic, 1976-1977 (Box 95, Folder 796)
    - Music Organizations - Young Audiences - National Committee, 1966-1978 (Box 95, Folder 797)
    - Music Organizations - Young Audiences - New York Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 95, Folder 798)
    - Music Organizations - Young Audiences - Miscellany, 1966-1977 (Box 95, Folder 799)
    - Theatre Organizations - General Material, 1975-1978 (Box 95, Folder 800)
    - Theatre Organizations - American Place Theatre, 1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 801)
    - Theatre Organizations - City Centers Young People's Theatre, 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 802)
    - Theatre Organizations - Cubiculo Theatre, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 803)
    - Theatre Organizations - New York Shakespeare Festival, 1973 (Box 96, Folder 804)
    - Theatre Organizations - O'Neill Memorial Theatre - Center Showboat, 1973-1975 (Box 96, Folder 805)
    - Theatre Organizations - O'Neill Memorial Theatre - Children's Theatre Symposium, n.d. (Box 96, Folder 806)
    - Theatre Organizations - Roundabout Theatre, 1974-1977 (Box 96, Folder 807)
    - Urban Organizations - Henry Street Settlement - Urban Life Center, 1974-1978 (Box 96, Folder 808)
    - Urban Organizations - New York Urban Coalition, 1975-1979 (Box 96, Folder 809)
    - Urban Organizations - New York Urban Coalition - Newsletters, 1974-1978 (Box 96, Folder 810)
- Arts in Education Program - Kathryn Bloom Files, 1967-1979; 11; 88 Cubic Feet 204 document cases
  Subseries A - Administration File, Subseries B - Project Files, Subseries C - Contact File
  Sound recordings; Moving Images
  - Art Safaris, 16 mm film, length: 27', color; Moving Image
  - IMPACT at Edgewood, 1971 June 15; Sound, Black and white, 30 minutes; 1 inch videotape (Reel AV 11565)
    Scope and Contents
    Program at KOAC-TV. Tape provided by Television Department, Eugene (Oregon) Public Schools.
    Access copy available.
  - Arts in Education Project Meeting in New York City, February 24-25, 1969; audio recording, 1 of 2 (Box AT 1, Folder 3)
    See also Box 115, Folder 933.
    Subseries A
  - Arts in Education Project Meeting in New York City, February 24-25, 1969; audio recording, 2 of 2 (Box AT 1, Folder 4)
    See also Box 115, Folder 933
  - Institute for the Study of Art in Education Meeting, May 2-3, 1969; audio recording (Box AT 1, Folder 5)
  - Central Midwestern Regional Educational Laboratory, Inc. (CEMREL) National Advisory Committee Meeting, May 22-23, 1969; audio recording (Box AT 1, Folder 6)
  - Conference on Advanced Placement in Art and Music, New York City, December 16, 1969; 1/4 inch audio tape (Box AT 1, Folder 7)
  - Network Meeting, Part I, April 9-10, 1970; audio recording, 1 of 2 (Box AT 1, Folder 8)
    See also Box 115, Folder 934
  - Network Meeting, Part II, April 9-10, 1970; audio recording, 2 of 2 (Box AT 1, Folder 9)
  - Network Writers' Meeting, New York City, June 9, 1970; audio recording (Box AT 1, Folder 10)
    See also Box 115, Folder 935
  - Educational Systems for the Seventies (ES '70) Conference, October 29-30, 1970; audio recording, 1 of 2 (Box AT 1, Folder 11)
  - Educational Systems for the Seventies (ES '70) Conference, October 29-30, 1970; audio recording, 2 of 2 (Box AT 1, Folder 12)
  - Seminar on Evaluation, July 16, 1971 (Box AT 2, Folder 13)
  - Project SEARCH Seminar, Westbury, New York, May 15-17, 1972; 1 of 3 (Box AT 2, Folder 14)
  - Project SEARCH Seminar, Westbury, New York, May 15-17, 1972; 2 of 3 (Box AT 2, Folder 15)
  - Project SEARCH Seminar, Westbury, New York, May 15-17, 1972; 3 of 3 (Box AT 2, Folder 16)
  - Young Audiences National Conference, Minneapolis - Keynote Address by Gene C. Wenner, May 6, 1973 (Box AT 2, Folder 17)
  - Washington State Meeting - Speech by Kathryn Bloom, October 25, 1973 (Box AT 2, Folder 18)
  - Staff Meeting, October 30, 1973 (Box AT 2, Folder 19)
  - Arthur Custer and Neil Postman (Box AT 2, Folder 20)
  - Professional Organizations - Reports, n.d. (Box AT 2, Folder 21)
  - Tape Labelled "Part I" (Box AT 2, Folder 22)
  - Tape Labelled "Part II" (Box AT 2, Folder 23)
  - Tape to Accompany Arts in Education Slides (Box AT 2, Folder 24)
  - Unidentified Tape, 1 of 2 (Box AT 2, Folder 25)
  - Unidentified Tape, 2 of 2 (Box AT 2, Folder 26)
  - Regional Meeting at John Adams High School, February 27, 1970; audio recording (Box C 1, Folder 1)
    Cassette tape.
  - Meeting at Santa Fe, New Mexico, July 18, 1970; audio recording, 1 of 3 (Box C 1, Folder 2)
  - Meeting at Santa Fe, New Mexico, July 18, 1970; audio recording, 2 of 3 (Box C 1, Folder 3)
  - Meeting at Santa Fe, New Mexico, July 18, 1970; audio recording, 3 of 3 (Box C 1, Folder 4)
  - University City Evaluation, October 29, 1973; audio recording (Box C 1, Folder 5)
  - Ruth Clark - Presentation of 1973 Yankelovich Youth Survey, audio recording (Box C 1, Folder 6)
  - Central Midwestern Regional Educational Laboratory, Inc. (CEMREL) Meeting, October 30, 1974; audio recording (Box C 1, Folder 7)
  - League of Cities Meeting, May 26-27, 1975; audio recording, 1 of 3 (Box C 1, Folder 8)
  - League of Cities Meeting, May 26-27, 1975; audio recording, 2 of 3 (Box C 1, Folder 9)
  - League of Cities Meeting, May 26-27, 1975; audio recording, 3 of 3 (Box C 1, Folder 10)
  - Kathryn Bloom at New York City Board of Education Meeting, October 14, 1975; audio recording (Box C 1, Folder 11)
  - Jefferson County (Colorado) Schools - Meeting, January 16, 1976; audio recording, 1 of 2 (Box C 1, Folder 12)
  - Jefferson County (Colorado) Schools - Meeting, January 16, 1976; audio recording, 2 of 2 (Box C 1, Folder 13)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Western Regional Meeting, February 19-20, 1976; audio recording, 1 of 4 (Box C 1, Folder 14)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Western Regional Meeting, February 19-20, 1976; audio recording, 2 of 4 (Box C 1, Folder 15)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Western Regional Meeting, February 19-20, 1976; audio recording, 3 of 4 (Box C 1, Folder 16)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Western Regional Meeting, February 19-20, 1976; audio recording, 4 of 4 (Box C 1, Folder 17)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Eastern Regional Meeting, February 26, 1976; audio recording, 1 of 2 (Box C 1, Folder 18)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States - Eastern Regional Meeting, February 26, 1976; audio recording (Box C 1, Folder 19)
  - League of Cities Meeting, Chicago, March 31-April 3, 1976; audio recording, 1 of 4 (Box C 2, Folder 20)
  - League of Cities Meeting, Chicago, March 31-April 3, 1976; audio recording, 2 of 4 (Box C 2, Folder 21)
  - League of Cities Meeting, Chicago, March 31-April 3, 1976; audio recording, 3 of 4 (Box C 2, Folder 22)
  - League of Cities Meeting, Chicago, March 31-April 3, 1976; audio recording, 4 of 4 (Box C 2, Folder 23)
  - Meeting on Dance, New York City, June 3, 1976; audio recording (Box C 2, Folder 24)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States Meeting, September 28-29, 1976; audio recording, 1 of 4 (Box C 2, Folder 25)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States Meeting, September 28-29, 1976; audio recording, 2 of 4 (Box C 2, Folder 26)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States Meeting, September 28-29, 1976; audio recording, 3 of 4 (Box C 2, Folder 27)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States Meeting, September 28-29, 1976; audio recording, 4 of 4 (Box C 2, Folder 28)
  - League of Cities Meeting, October 13-15, 1976; audio recording, 1 of 5 (Box C 2, Folder 29)
  - League of Cities Meeting, October 13-15, 1976; audio recording, 2 of 5 (Box C 2, Folder 30)
  - League of Cities Meeting, October 13-15, 1976; audio recording, 3 of 5 (Box C 2, Folder 31)
  - League of Cities Meeting, October 13-15, 1976; audio recording, 4 of 5 (Box C 2, Folder 32)
  - League of Cities Meeting, October 13-15, 1976; audio recording, 5 of 5 (Box C 2, Folder 33)
  - Oklahoma City Meeting - Clyde McGeary Speech, December 2, 1976; audio recording (Box C 2, Folder 34)
  - League of Cities Meeting, December 9-10, 1976; audio recording, 1 of 3 (Box C 2, Folder 35)
  - League of Cities Meeting, December 9-10, 1976; audio recording, 2 of 3 (Box C 2, Folder 36)
  - League of Cities Meeting, December 9-10, 1976; audio recording, 3 of 3 (Box C 2, Folder 37)
  - League of Cities Meeting, December 9-10, 1976; audio recording (Box C 3, Folder 38)
  - Arts in Education Conference, May 3, 1977; audio recording, 1 of 5 (Box C 3, Folder 39)
    See also Box 115, Folders 937-940
  - Arts in Education Conference, May 3, 1977; audio recording, 2 of 5 (Box C 3, Folder 40)
  - Arts in Education Conference, May 3, 1977; audio recording, 3 of 5 (Box C 3, Folder 41)
  - Arts in Education Conference, May 3, 1977; audio recording, 4 of 5 (Box C 3, Folder 42)
  - Arts in Education Conference, May 3, 1977; audio recording, 5 of 5 (Box C 3, Folder 43)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States Meeting, Oklahoma City, September 30, 1977; audio recording, 1 of 3 (Box C 3, Folder 44)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States Meeting, Oklahoma City, September 30, 1977; audio recording, 2 of 3 (Box C 3, Folder 45)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States Meeting, Oklahoma City, September 30, 1977; audio recording, 3 of 3 (Box C 3, Folder 46)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States Meeting, May 23-24, 1978; audio recording (Box C 3, Folder 47)
  - Nola Whitman Presentation, August 10, 1978; audio recording (Box C 3, Folder 48)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States Meeting, September 19-23, 1978; audio recording, 1 of 4 (Box C 3, Folder 49)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States Meeting, September 19-23, 1978; audio recording, 2 of 4 (Box C 3, Folder 50)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States Meeting, September 19-23, 1978; audio recording, 3 of 4 (Box C 3, Folder 51)
  - Ad Hoc Coalition of States Meeting, September 19-23, 1978; audio recording, 4 of 4 (Box C 3, Folder 52)
  - AAE Meeting, audio recording, 1 of 2 (Box C 3, Folder 53)
  - AAE Meeting, audio recording, 2 of 2 (Box C 3, Folder 54)
  - AAE Meeting, audio recording, 1 of 3 (Box C 4, Folder 55)
  - AAE Meeting, audio recording, 2 of 3 (Box C 4, Folder 56)
  - AAE Meeting, audio recording, 3 of 3 (Box C 4, Folder 57)
  - Arts in Education Committee Meeting, December 4; audio recording, 1 of 2 (Box C 4, Folder 58)
  - Arts in Education Committee Meeting, December 4; audio recording, 2 of 2 (Box C 4, Folder 59)
  - Kathryn Bloom, n.d.; audio recording, 1 of 2 (Box C 4, Folder 60)
  - Kathryn Bloom, n.d.; audio recording, 2 of 2 (Box C 4, Folder 61)
  - CASE Session, n.d.; audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 62)
  - Central Midwestern Regional Educational Laboratory, Inc. (CEMREL), October 30; audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 63)
  - Coalition/Data Collection, audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 64)
  - Goodlad, Howe, and Keppell, audio recording, 1 of 2 (Box C 4, Folder 65)
  - Goodlad, Howe, and Keppell, audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 66)
  - Institute for Development of Educational Activities (IDEA) - Process and Skills Workshop, audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 67)
  - Japan (Joyce Raessler), n.d.; audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 68)
  - Mexico - Notes, n.d.; audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 69)
  - Motivational Environments (Charles Battaglini), n.d.; audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 70)
  - Oklahoma City - Opening Doors, n.d.; audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 71)
  - Soundscape, audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 72)
  - Special Arts, n.d.; audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 73)
  - Unidentified Tape, audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 74)
  - Unidentified Tape, audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 75)
  - Unidentified Tape, audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 76)
  - Unidentified Tape, audio recording (Box C 4, Folder 77)
  - Arts in Education Program - Kathryn Bloom Files - Administration File, 11.A
    This subseries consists of annual report material, correspondence, day files, financial material, interoffice memoranda, personnel and publication material, and speeches by staff members.
    - Annual Reports - Typescripts, 1972-1977 (Box 97, Folder 811)
    - Annual Reports - Typescripts, 1972-1977 (Box 97, Folder 812)
    - Annual Reports - Correspondence, 1971-1976 (Box 97, Folder 813)
    - Consultants - General, 1969-1979 (Box 97, Folder 814)
    - Consultants - Aldridge, Gary, 1969-1970 (Box 97, Folder 815)
    - Consultants - Grove, Richard, 1969-1975 (Box 97, Folder 816)
    - Consultants - Hausman, Jerome J., 1968-1975 (Box 97, Folder 817)
    - Consultants - Hausman, Jerome J. - Travel Expenses, 1969-1975 (Box 97, Folder 818)
    - Consultants - Josman, Martin, 1972 (Box 97, Folder 819)
    - Consultants - Malcolm, Christian T., 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 820)
    - Consultants - Moss, Elaine, 1972-1978 (Box 98, Folder 821)
    - Consultants - Oliver, Andrew C., 1971-1975 (Box 98, Folder 822)
    - Consultants - Shuker, Nancy, 1977-1978 (Box 98, Folder 823)
    - Consultants - Young, Marjorie, 1974-1977 (Box 98, Folder 824)
    - Consultants - Conference, October 2-3, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 825)
    - Consultants - Conference, October 2-3, 1969 (Box 98, Folder 826)
    - Consultants - Consulting Services, 1968-1970 (Box 98, Folder 827)
    - Correspondence (A-Al) (Box 98, Folder 828)
    - Correspondence (Am-Az) (Box 98, Folder 829)
    - Correspondence (Ba-Bo) (Box 99, Folder 830)
    - Correspondence (Br-Bu) (Box 99, Folder 831)
    - Correspondence - Burris-Meyer, Harold, 1969-1975 (Box 99, Folder 832)
    - Correspondence - Burris-Meyer, Harold - Reports, 1968-1974 (Box 99, Folder 833)
    - Correspondence - Burris-Meyer, Harold - Reports, 1968-1974 (Box 99, Folder 834)
    - Correspondence (C) (Box 100, Folder 835)
    - Correspondence (Da-Di) (Box 100, Folder 836)
    - Correspondence (Do-Dz) (Box 100, Folder 837)
    - Correspondence (E) (Box 100, Folder 838)
    - Correspondence (F) (Box 100, Folder 839)
    - Correspondence (G) (Box 100, Folder 840)
    - Correspondence (Ha-Hoc) (Box 101, Folder 841)
    - Correspondence - Hoffa, Harlan, 1968-1977 (Box 101, Folder 842)
    - Correspondence (Hof-Iz) (Box 101, Folder 843)
    - Correspondence (J) (Box 101, Folder 844)
    - Correspondence (K) (Box 101, Folder 845)
    - Correspondence (La) (Box 101, Folder 846)
    - Correspondence (Le-Lz) (Box 102, Folder 847)
    - Correspondence (M) (Box 102, Folder 848)
    - Correspondence (N) (Box 102, Folder 849)
    - Correspondence (O-Pa) (Box 102, Folder 850)
    - Correspondence (Pe-Qz) (Box 102, Folder 851)
    - Correspondence (R) (Box 102, Folder 852)
    - Correspondence (Sa) (Box 103, Folder 853)
    - Correspondence (Sc) (Box 103, Folder 854)
    - Correspondence (Se-Sp) (Box 103, Folder 855)
    - Correspondence - Stake, Robert E., 1971-1976 (Box 103, Folder 856)
    - Correspondence (St-Sz) (Box 103, Folder 857)
    - Correspondence (T) (Box 103, Folder 858)
    - Correspondence (U-Wh) (Box 104, Folder 859)
    - Correspondence (Wi-Z) (Box 104, Folder 860)
    - Day Files, January-June; 1972 (Box 104, Folder 861)
    - Day Files, January-June; 1972 (Box 104, Folder 862)
    - Day Files, January-June; 1972 (Box 104, Folder 863)
    - Day Files, January-June; 1972 (Box 104, Folder 864)
    - Day Files, January-June; 1972 (Box 104, Folder 865)
    - Day Files, July 1972-February 1973 (Box 105, Folder 866)
    - Day Files, July 1972-February 1973 (Box 105, Folder 867)
    - Day Files, July 1972-February 1973 (Box 105, Folder 868)
    - Day Files, July 1972-February 1973 (Box 105, Folder 869)
    - Day Files, July 1972-February 1973 (Box 105, Folder 870)
    - Day Files, July 1972-February 1973 (Box 105, Folder 871)
    - Day Files, March-September 1973 (Box 106, Folder 872)
    - Day Files, March-September 1973 (Box 106, Folder 873)
    - Day Files, March-September 1973 (Box 106, Folder 874)
    - Day Files, March-September 1973 (Box 106, Folder 875)
    - Day Files, March-September 1973 (Box 106, Folder 876)
    - Day Files, March-September 1973 (Box 106, Folder 877)
    - Day Files, March-September 1973 (Box 106, Folder 878)
    - Day Files, October 1973-April 1974 (Box 107, Folder 879)
    - Day Files, October 1973-April 1974 (Box 107, Folder 880)
    - Day Files, October 1973-April 1974 (Box 107, Folder 881)
    - Day Files, October 1973-April 1974 (Box 107, Folder 882)
    - Day Files, October 1973-April 1974 (Box 107, Folder 883)
    - Day Files, October 1973-April 1974 (Box 107, Folder 884)
    - Day Files, May-November 1974 (Box 108, Folder 885)
    - Day Files, May-November 1974 (Box 108, Folder 886)
    - Day Files, May-November 1974 (Box 108, Folder 887)
    - Day Files, May-November 1974 (Box 108, Folder 888)
    - Day Files, May-November 1974 (Box 108, Folder 889)
    - Day Files, May-November 1974 (Box 108, Folder 890)
    - Day Files, May-November 1974 (Box 108, Folder 891)
    - Day Files, December 1974-June 1975 (Box 109, Folder 892)
    - Day Files, December 1974-June 1975 (Box 109, Folder 893)
    - Day Files, December 1974-June 1975 (Box 109, Folder 894)
    - Day Files, December 1974-June 1975 (Box 109, Folder 895)
    - Day Files, December 1974-June 1975 (Box 109, Folder 896)
    - Day Files, December 1974-June 1975 (Box 109, Folder 897)
    - Day Files, July 1975-February 1976 (Box 110, Folder 898)
    - Day Files, July 1975-February 1976 (Box 110, Folder 899)
    - Day Files, July 1975-February 1976 (Box 110, Folder 900)
    - Day Files, July 1975-February 1976 (Box 110, Folder 901)
    - Day Files, July 1975-February 1976 (Box 110, Folder 902)
    - Day Files, July 1975-February 1976 (Box 110, Folder 903)
    - Day Files, July 1975-February 1976 (Box 110, Folder 904)
    - Day Files, July 1975-February 1976 (Box 110, Folder 905)
    - Day Files, March 1976-March 1977 (Box 111, Folder 906)
    - Day Files, March 1974-March 1977 (Box 111, Folder 907)
    - Day Files, March 1974-March 1977 (Box 111, Folder 908)
    - Day Files, March 1974-March 1977 (Box 111, Folder 909)
    - Day Files, March 1974-March 1977 (Box 111, Folder 910)
    - Day Files, March 1974-March 1977 (Box 111, Folder 911)
    - Day Files, April 1977-May 1978 (Box 112, Folder 912)
    - Day Files, April 1977-May 1978 (Box 112, Folder 913)
    - Day Files, April 1977-May 1978 (Box 112, Folder 914)
    - Day Files, April 1977-May 1978 (Box 112, Folder 915)
    - Day Files, April 1977-May 1978 (Box 112, Folder 916)
    - Day Files, April 1977-May 1978 (Box 112, Folder 917)
    - Day Files, June 1978-June 1979 (Box 113, Folder 918)
    - Day Files, June 1978-June 1979 (Box 113, Folder 919)
    - Day Files, June 1978-June 1979 (Box 113, Folder 920)
    - Day Files, June 1978-June 1979 (Box 113, Folder 921)
    - Day Files, June 1978-June 1979 (Box 113, Folder 922)
    - Evaluation - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 113, Folder 923)
    - Evaluation - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 113, Folder 924)
    - Evaluation - Report and Supporting Materials, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 925)
    - Evaluation - Report (Revision), 1973 (Box 114, Folder 926)
    - Evaluation - Payment File, 1973 (Box 114, Folder 927)
    - Evaluation - Conferences, 1971-1974 (Box 114, Folder 928)
    - Evaluation - Conferences, 1971-1974 (Box 114, Folder 929)
    - Expenses, 1969-1972 (Box 114, Folder 930)
    - Finance - Budget Compliance Form, 1968-1970 (Box 114, Folder 931)
    - Invitations - Declinations, 1974-1979 (Box 114, Folder 932)
    - Meetings - Arts in Education, New York, February 24-25, 1969 (Box 115, Folder 933)
    - Meetings - Project Network, New York, April 9-10, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 934)
    - Meetings - Project Directors, New York, June 9, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 935)
    - Meetings - Education of School Administrators, New York, April 15-16, December 9, 27, 1971 (Box 115, Folder 936)
    - Meetings - Arts in Education, Chicago, May 3-5, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 937)
      Correspondence, Response File, Transcript and Report, and Post-Conference Follow-up.
    - Meetings - Arts in Education, Chicago, May 3-5, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 938)
    - Meetings - Arts in Education, Chicago, May 3-5, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 939)
    - Meetings - Arts in Education, Chicago, May 3-5, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 940)
    - Memberships, 1969-1977 (Box 116, Folder 941)
    - Memberships, 1969-1977 (Box 116, Folder 942)
    - Memberships, 1969-1977 (Box 116, Folder 943)
    - Memoranda - For the Record, 1973-1976 (Box 116, Folder 944)
    - Memoranda - Interstaff, 1967-1977 (Box 116, Folder 945)
    - Memoranda - Interstaff, 1967-1977 (Box 116, Folder 946)
    - Memoranda - Interstaff, 1967-1977 (Box 116, Folder 947)
    - Memoranda - To Room 5600, 1968-1979 (Box 117, Folder 948)
    - Memoranda - From Room 5600, 1968-1977 (Box 117, Folder 949)
    - Orders, 1969-1979 (Box 117, Folder 950)
    - Papers - Aldridge, Gary, 1969 (Box 117, Folder 951)
    - Papers - Bloom, Kathryn, 1969-1978 (Box 117, Folder 952)
    - Papers - Bloom, Kathryn, 1969-1978 (Box 117, Folder 953)
    - Papers - Bloom, Kathryn, 1969-1978 (Box 117, Folder 954)
    - Papers (Box 117, Folder 955)